Finding Aid for the John Povey Papers LSC.0452
UCLA Library Special Collections
John Povey papers
1958-1992
UCLA Library Special Collections
Povey, John F., 1929-1992
LSC.0452
17.5 linear feet (35 boxes and 1 oversize box)
The papers of UCLA professor John Povey consist of manuscripts, notes, printed material, publications, drawings, and correspondence related to his teaching, research, and administrative activities, including the editorship of the journal African Arts.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Gail Povey, February 1996.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9950463143606533
Biography
John Frederick Povey was born April 5, 1929 in South London. Povey was educated at St. Dunstan's College in London during the Blitz. After World War II, Povey was employed in a gold mine in South Africa under a plan that allowed him to study at the University of South Africa in Pretoria, where he completed a B.A. in English (1956) and an M.A. in Teaching English as a Second Language (1960). In the United States, Povey completed his Ph.D. in Third World Literature in English at Michigan State University (1964), after which he joined the faculty at UCLA. His areas of research included South African and Nigerian literature, comparative world literature, language planning and policy, ESL/TESL, and investigating symbols and rituals in African art. John Povey's career at UCLA was distinguished. He was director of the African Humanities Institute, chair of the ESL Section of the English Department, chair of the Africa Committee of the UC Education Abroad Program, Associate Director of the African Studies Center, and Project Director for numerous in-service teacher training programs in the United States and Africa. He authored eight books and texts, 20 chapters for edited volumes, and more than 100 reviews and articles on African literature, art, and culture. His field research took him to Nigeria, Ghana, Senegal, Kenya, South Africa, Rwanda, Zaire, Cameroon, Zimbabwe, Somalia, Togo, and Liberia. One of his most signifigant acomplishments at UCLA was his notable editorship of African Arts, in which he served from Fall 1967 until his retirement in 1991. His tireless efforts to have all forms of African art included in the major canon of art history promoted the work of talented African artists globally. He died of cancer on May 3, 1992.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of manuscripts, notes, printed material, publications, drawings, and correspondence related to his teaching, research, and administrative activities, including the editorship of the journal African Arts. Notable items include promotional materials from galleries empasizing African art, research files on Nigerian Shona artists, and personal correspondence with Tayo Olafioye, Dumile, and Dennis Brutus. The files document Professor Povey's varied interests, including English literacy through literature, and African art.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Student theses and dissertations, 1973-1991
Research and teaching, 1958-1992
African Arts, 1965-1992
Publications and manuscripts, 1965-1991
Miscellaneous professional papers, 1968-1992
The collection was initally sorted and boxed by Gail Povey prior to acquisition by UCLA Special Collections. For processing, files were removed from the labeled cartons, rehoused, and organized into five series reflecting the original order of the papers as found in the cartons.
Africanists -- United States -- Archives.; Povey, John F., 1929-1992 -- Archives
- Series I: Student Theses and Dissertations, 1973-1991; 7 boxes (3.5 linear ft.)
  Scope and Contents note
  Series I consists of student articles, prospectuses, theses and dissertations.
  General note
  Files are arranged alphabetically by author surname.
  - Abiedu, Julius Peka., 1989; (1 item). (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Science and Technology Education in Cameroon.
  - Admassu, Yonas., 1991; (1 item). (Box 1, Folder 2)
    T'Obbiya, Ethiopia, and Utopia.
  - Ahmed, Ali Jimale., 1989; (1 item). (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Tradition, Anomaly, and the Wave for the Future.
  - Asante, Charles Cofie., 1984; (1 item). (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Induced Lexical Solecisms.
  - Badejo, Deirdre L.G., 1984; (1 item). (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Yoruba Theater.
  - Dally, Patrice Anita., 1984; (1 item). (Box 1, Folder 6)
    An Experiment in Methods of Assessing Difficulty in Literature for ESL Readers.
  - Dukleth, Kurt Ervin., 1985; (1 item). (Box 2, Folder 1)
    A Comparison of American and Soviet Policy.
  - Egejuru, Phanuel Akubueze., 1973; (1 item). (Box 2, Folder 2)
    The Influence of Audience on West African Novels.
  - Faye, Deirdre., 1990; (1 item). (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Peer Editing in the Community College ESL Classroom.
  - Fonseca, Mary Louise., 1980; (1 item). (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Objectives and Bibliography for an American Literature Course for ESL Students.
  - Gader, Rachel., n.d.; (1 item). (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Curriculum Development and Materials Design for the 33C graduate Section of the ESL Svc. Courses at UCLA.
  - Geisler, James., 1979; (1 item). (Box 2, Folder 6)
    The Development of the English Departments of Four African Universities.
  - Gerbault, Jeannine., 1979; (1 item). (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Language and Language Policy in Senegal.
  - Giber, Maidy Lee., 1988; (1 item). (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Curriculum and Materials Development for a Sheltered Anthropology Course in the EFL Context.
  - Hepburn, Joan E., 1985; (2 items). (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Toward the Reintegration of Society.
  - Ho, Yvonne., 1991; (1 item). (Box 3, Folder 4)
    The Role of Non Scripted and Scripted Video in Foreign Language Teaching.
  - Johnson, Cathy., 1991; (1 item). (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Gender Differences in Perception and Usage of Profanity.
  - Katrak, Ketu (Katy) S., 1982; (1 item). (Box 3, Folder 6)
    The Tragic Drama of Wole Soyinka.
  - Larson, Kazue Fujinuma., 1991; (1 item). (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Temporality in Modern Japanese Narratives.
  - Lederer, Mary Susan., 1991; (1 item). (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Tsitsi Dangarembga, Bessie Head, and Doris Lessing: The Social Context of Madness.
  - Lee, Cynthia Chin-Wan., 1986; (1 item). (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Language Policy in Singapore.
  - Loomis, De Wayne Jr., 1984; (1 item). (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Language Planning: Turkey as a Case Study.
  - Ma, Li., 1984; (1 item). (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Teaching English through Drama to Chinese Students.
  - Malliagh, Ronald., 1991; (1 item). (Box 4, Folder 6)
    The 1980s Educational Reform Movement in England.
  - Miles, Norma Dorothy., 1979; (1 item). (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Toward Domesticating the English Literature Curriculum of Jamaican Schools.
  - Mitchell, Bonnie L., 1985; (1 item). (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Vocabulary Limitation in Simplified Literature for ESL Students.
  - Mithal, Gita Singh., 1974; (1 item). (Box 5, Folder 2)
    English-Language Teaching at Christ Church College, Kanpur, India.
  - Mtonga, Mapopa., 1984; (6 items). (Box 5, Folder 3)
    The Drama of Gule Wamkulu.
    Also, 3pp. of photos and 2 letters to John Povey.
  - November, Melvyn Douglas., 1988; (1 item). (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Historical Considerations in the Formulation of Language Policy in South Africa.
  - O'Neal, Karen Louise., 1989; (1 item). (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Educational Language Policy in Three Sub-Saharan African Countries.
  - Ochsner, Robert Steven., 1977; (1 item). (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Role of the South Pacific Commission in Regional Language Policies.
  - Semali, Ladislaus (1 of 2)., 1988; (1 item). (Box 5, Folder 7)
    A Study of Post-Literacy and Adult Literacy Retention in Tanzania.
  - Semali, Ladislaus (2 of 2)., 1990; (1 item). (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Postliteracy in Tanzania and the Retention of Literacy Skills in Adults.
  - Smith, Narcissa., 1991; (1 item). (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Language as a Critical Principle in Africa Literature at Home and in Diaspora.
  - Stern, Susan Louise (1 of 2)., 1985; (1 item). (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Teaching Literature in ESL/EFL: An Integrative Approach.
  - Stern, Susan Louise (2 of 2)., 1977; (1 item). (Box 7, Folder 1)
    The Teaching of Contemporary American Drama in Advanced ESL.
  - Thornton, Elizabeth Ann., 1980; (1 item). (Box 7, Folder 2)
    A Needs Analysis for a Multi-Language Degree Program in Tunisia.
  - Trechter, Sherry Lee., 1983; (1 item). (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Towards an Intermediate English Course Based on African Folktales.
  - Williams, Kathleen Ann., 1987; (1 item). (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Getting to the Roots of American Culture.
- Series II: Research Project Files, 1958-1992; 13 boxes (7.5 linear ft.)
  Series II consists of files relating to John Povey's major research areas.
  Series II is organized into four subseries:
  Subseries IIA: Bureau of Indian Affairs, 1967-1983
  Subseries IIB: African literature, 1964-1991
  Subseries IIC: Language projects, 1958-1991
  Subseries IID: ESL/TESL, 1963-1992
  - Subseries IIA: Bureau of Indian Affairs, 1967-1983
    Series IIA consists of articles, student work, BIA school newsletters, Native American art exhibition materials, and curriculum material.
    - Art., ca. 1970-1980; (11 items). (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Gallery publications and printed material related to Native American Art.
      See Box 36 for original ink drawings.
    - Articles and newsletters., 1968-1973; (17 items). (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Articles and newsletters on BIA
    - Creative writing program., 1968-1973; (ca. 15 items). (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Assorted materials re the BIA Creative Writing Program.
    - Curriculum development., 1971; (1 item). (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Manual.
    - Journals., 1969-1972; (3 items). (Box 8, Folder 3)
      "Linguistic-cultural differences and American education" in Florida FL Reporter journal
      Southwest Review
      Contemporary Alaskan Literature
    - Program files., 1968-1973; (12 items). (Box 8, Folder 4)
      Assorted program files and BIA literature.
    - School files (1 of 2)., 1967-1983; (28 items). (Box 8, Folder 5)
      Assorted writings and literature from BIA school and students.
    - School files (2 of 2)., 1967-1974; (16 items). (Box 8, Folder 6)
      Assorted writings by and about BIA schools.
  - Subseries IIB: African Literature, 1964-1991
    Series IIB consists of articles, student exams, literary reviews, and correspondence from poets Dan Rakgoathe and Oyekan Owomoyele.
    - Articles., 1966-1991 (Box 9, Folder 1-5)
      Various printed articles.
      - 1966-1991, (12 items). (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - ca. 1970, (10 items). (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - 1970-1989, (15 items). (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - 1966-1989, (14 items). (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - 1965-1984, (11 items). (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - African Literature Association., 1965-1970; (13 items). (Box 9, Folder 6)
      Various correspondence and material from ALA.
    - African Literature Exam., 1966-1985; (31 items). (Box 9, Folder 7)
      Exams.
    - Australia., 1977-1986; (8 items). (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Assorted printed material.
    - Correspondence., 1966-1985; (7 items). (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Various types of correspondence.
    - Eng Lit 271, 285., 1972-1986; (8 items). (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Course materials.
    - Literary criticism and review., 1964-1993 (Box 10, Folder 2-5)
      Assorted printed review material.
      - 1964-1978, (13 items). (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - 1964-1966, (8 items). (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - 1966-1981, (14 items). (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - 1966-1993, (ca. 30 items). (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous., 1966-1991; (ca. 20 items). (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Miscellaneous correspondence and printed materials.
    - Owomoyela, Oyekan., 1985-1991; (6 items). (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Correspondence.
    - Project files., 1976-1992; (5 items). (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Assorted correspondence and printed materials.
    - Poetry/Prose., ca. 1980; (35 items). (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Various printed materials on poetry.
    - Program Proposal., 1969-1974; (3 items). (Box 11, Folder 3)
      Printed material on proposed graduate programs for the M.A./PhD. in African Languages/Lit.
    - Rakgoathe, Dan--poetry., 1981-1988; (11 items). (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Assorted printed material from poet Rakgoathe, Dan.
    - South African literature (1 of 3), 1984-1988; (24 items). (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Various book reviews on South African literature.
      See Box 36 for oversized poster.
    - South African literature (2 of 3)., 1978-1987; (45 items). (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Various printed materials.
    - South African literature (3 of 3)., 1965-1990; (27 items). (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - South African theory., 1971-1982; (3 items). (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Articles.
    - Teaching Materials., 1965-1970; (5 items). (Box 11, Folder 9)
      Various printed materials on curriculum development.
  - Subseries IIC: Language Projects, 1958-1991
    Series IIC consists of materials related to A Sociolinguistic Profile of Urban Centers in Cameroon, journals, conference materials, ESL policy files, an unfinished language policy manuscript, and assorted printed materials.
    - American Education--Africa., 1969 and 1985-1988 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
      Various printed materials on American education principles in Africa.
      - 1985-1988, (3 items). (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - ca. 1969, (2 items). (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Cameroon., 1976-1982 (Box 12, Folder 3-5)
      Various files on English language project.
      - 1976-1981, (17 items). (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - 1976-1982, (22 items). (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - 1976-1979, (25 items). (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Cameroon Urban Centers., 1981-1984; (6 items). (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Bound book edited by Povey, Koenig, Edna L., and Chia, Emmanuel, Chia with correspondence from publishers. A Sociolinguistic Profile of Urban Centers in Cameroon.
    - China., 1972-1988; (22 items). (Box 12, Folder 7)
      Assorted documents re visit to Fudan University and language policy in China.
    - Developing nations., 1970-1989; (12 items). (Box 12, Folder 8)
      Various files on English language projects.
    - Commonwealth literature., 1968; (8 items). (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Comparative literature (1 of 2)., ca. 1970; (3 items). (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Assorted printed global short stories.
    - Comparative literature (2 of 2)., 1975-1991; (26 items). (Box 13, Folder 3)
      Assorted printed global short stories and other printed materials.
    - Francophone Africa., 1973-1975; (17 items). (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Indian English., 1968-1976; (10 items). (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Assorted documents on English language projects.
    - Imfundo Trust., 1989-1990; (5 items). (Box 13, Folder 6)
      Project files.
    - I.S.E.A., 1964-1965; (10 items). (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Project files on the Institute for the Study of English in Africa.
    - Journals., 1966-1990 (Box 13, Folder 8-9)
      Various bound language policy journals.
      - 1967-1990, (5 items). (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - 1966-1990, (6 items). (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Journals--Uganda., 1972; (2 items). (Box 14, Folder 1)
      Bound journal from Uganda, Bulletin of the Association for Commonwealth Literature and Language Studies.
    - Language Planning., 1966-1981; (6 items). (Box 14, Folder 2)
      Various articles of language planning.
    - Language--Philippines., 1962; (1 item). (Box 14, Folder 3)
      Unbound manuscript on English literature in Philippines.
    - Linkage files., 1987-1988; (2 items). (Box 14, Folder 4)
      Correspondence between National University of Lesotho and UCLA.
    - Language Ecology Conference., 1990-1991; (10 items). (Box 14, Folder 5)
      Various documents related to Language Ecology Conference.
    - Language Planning--Africa., 1967-1989; (12 items). (Box 14, Folder 6)
      Assorted printed materials.
    - Language policy., 1971-1991; (4 folders). (Box 14, Box 15)
      - 1972-1991, (11 items). (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - 1976-1991, (11 items). (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - 1982-1986, (31 items). (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - 1971-1991, (ca. 30 items). (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Molteno project., 1978-1985; (11 items). (Box 15, Folder 2)
      Various documents related to Molteno Project.
    - University of Namibia., 1990-1991; (4 items). (Box 15, Folder 3)
      Various documents related to University of Namibia.
    - Papua New Guinea., 1984-1990; (25 items). (Box 15, Folder 4)
      Assorted documents on English language projects from Joseph Nidue and University of Papua New Guinea.
    - Rwanda., 1973-1974; (25 items). (Box 15, Folder 5)
      Various letters requesting ESL teachers.
    - Singapore., 1988; (1 item). (Box 15, Folder 6)
      Request letter.
    - Somalia., 1982-1985; (8 items). (Box 15, Folder 7)
      Assorted EFL Project files.
    - South Africa., 1987-1991; (12 items). (Box 15, Folder 8)
      Various printed materials on language policy.
    - Soviet Union., ca. 1971; (4 items). (Box 15, Folder 9)
      Assorted printed materials on USSR.
    - Swaziland., 1987-1990; (13 items). (Box 15, Folder 10)
      Various printed materials on visit to Swaziland.
    - TESL--Africa (1 of 2)., 1963-1974; (10 items). (Box 15, Folder 11)
      Assorted printed articles in French and English on English in Africa.
    - TESL--Africa (2 of 2)., 1966-1981; (9 items). (Box 15, Folder 12)
      Various printed conference papers and articles, especially re Nigeria.
    - Togo Conference/EAP., 1985-1987; (16 items). (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Assorted materials on English Abroad Program.
    - Togo linkages (1 of 4)., 1977-1987; (24 items). (Box 16, Folder 2)
      Various printed materials on program.
    - Togo linkages (2 of 4)., 1983-1987; (26 items). (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Togo linkages (3 of 4)., 1982-1987; (26 items). (Box 16, Folder 4)
      Various printed materials on Togo.
    - Togo linkages (4 of 4)., 1981-1984; (15 items). (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - 280K Class Files., 1967-1990; (35 items). (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
      - 1967-1990, (35 items). (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - 1985-1990, (20 items). (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - U.K. Local Exams., 1958-1965; (13 items). (Box 17, Folder 3)
      Various English proficiency exams from Cambridge and University of London.
    - Zaire report., 1974; (1 item). (Box 17, Folder 4)
      English project final report.
    - Zaire., 1972-1974; (10 items). (Box 17, Folder 5)
      Various materials on English program.
    - Zimbabwe., 1972, 1988; (2 items). (Box 17, Folder 6)
      Assorted materials on Zimbabwe education.
    - Bame, Kwabena Nyamekye., 1991; (1 item). (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Letter of recommendation.
    - Bilingualism., 1978-1979; (4 items). (Box 18, Folder 2)
      Articles on bilingualism Peter Stevens.
    - Center for the Study of Comparative Folklore and Methodology., 1991; (1 item). (Box 18, Folder 3)
      Annual report.
    - Class notes--106J, K., 1966-1990 (Box 18, Folder 4-6)
      Exams, tests, student work, and articles.
      - 106J, K., 1966-1985; (21 items). (Box 18, Folder 4)
        Exams and tests.
      - 109J., 1966-1990; (113 items). (Box 18, Folder 5)
        Exams, student work, and articles.
      - 109K., 1966-1990; (ca. 50 items). (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Cultural hurdles., 1967, 1973; (2 items). (Box 18, Folder 7)
      Articles on cultural hurdles in ESL.
    - ESL files., 1960-1991; (ca. 40 items). (Box 18, Folder 8)
      Assorted clippings and printed material relating to ESL/TESL.
    - ESL/TESL UCLA reports., 1974-1991; (12 items). (Box 18, Folder 9)
      Departmental and section program reviews and reports.
    - ESL--Printed material., 1963-1987 (Box 19, Folder 1-3)
      Assorted handbooks and papers on ESL.
      - 1973-1987, (4 items). (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - 1963-1972, (3 items). (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - 1978-1979, (2 items). (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - ESL--Teaching with literature., 1980-1991; (16 items). (Box 19, Folder 4)
      Assorted materials on ESL/TESL and teaching with literature.
    - ESL in Africa., 1966-1977; (17 items). (Box 19, Folder 5)
      Journals, newsletters, and articles.
      See also Box 36 for oversized journals.
    - English Speaking Union., 1973-1975; (3 items). (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Language., 1960-1991; (ca. 15 items). (Box 20, Folder 1)
      Assorted articles, essays, and clippings on language.
    - Literature and ESL., 1964-1990; (42 items). (Box 20, Folder 2)
      Assorted materials on ESL and literature.
    - Lithuania., 1978-1990; (4 items). (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Proposal., 1973; (1 item). (Box 20, Folder 4)
      Proposal for the establishment of a Center of Comparative Study of Non- Western Humanities.
    - Obiajuru, Maduakor., 1979-1992 (Box 20, Folder 5-6)
      Articles and publications.
      - 1979-1992, (20 items). (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - 1982-1986, (10 items). (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - SACDFP., 1990-1991; (27 items). (Box 20, Folder 7)
      Project file for South African Career Development Fellows.
    - TESL., 1965-1991; (5 folders) (Box 20, Box 21)
      - TESL Articles., 1965-1991; (7 items). (Box 20, Folder 8)
        Assorted printed material re teaching English using literature and drama.
      - TESL Essays., n.d.; (12 items). (Box 28, Folder 9)
        Essays by Povey re teaching English using literature and drama.
      - TESL--Swaziland., 1972; (1 item). (Box 20, Folder 10)
        Scheme for the improvement of African education.
      - TESL African language policy (1 of 2)., 1966-1978; (9 items). (Box 21, Folder 1)
        Papers related to language policy in Africa.
      - TESL African language policy (2 of 2)., 1967-1971; (20 items). (Box 21, Folder 2)
        Papers and news bulletins related to language policy in Africa.
- Series III: African Arts, 1965-1992; 5 boxes (2.5 linear ft.)
  Series III consists of articles, symposium programs, reviews, lecture notes, journals, artwork from visual artists Owiti and Tayo Adnaike, photographs, gallery publications, and promotional material for the 1966 World Festival of Negro Arts.
  - ACASA., 1987-1989; (2 items). (Box 21, Folder 3)
    Arts Council of the African Studies Association roster and newsletter.
  - Achebe, Chinua., 1990; (13 items). (Box 21, Folder 4)
    Assorted symposium materials.
  - African art (1 of 2)., 1970-1991; (ca. 40 items). (Box 21, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, articles, clippings, and printed materials on African art.
  - African art (2 of 2)., 1967-1991; (23 items). (Box 21, Folder 6)
    Various printed materials on African art.
  - African Art--Book reviews., 1974-1975; (7 items). (Box 21, Folder 7)
    Various book reviews on African art.
  - African Art--Exhibits., 1973-1987; (15 items). (Box 21, Folder 8)
    Assorted printed materials on exhibits.
  - African Art Foundation., 1983-1984; (6 items). (Box 21, Folder 9)
    AAF correspondence.
  - African Arts Magazine., 1967-1990; (24 items). (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Correspondence and printed materials about African Arts.
  - African Arts Magazine--Book project., n.d.; (10 items). (Box 22, Folder 2)
    Unfinished chapter ideas and information.
  - African Arts Magazine--Finances., 1972-1989; (ca. 40 items). (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Financial documents, correspondence, and clippings related to the funding of African Arts.
  - African Arts Magazine--Submissions., 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 4-5)
    Various printed materials and photos not accepted for publication.
    - 1987-1988, (13 items). (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - 1987, (20 items). (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Owiti, Hezlon E., n.d.; (1 item). (Box 22, Folder 6)
    Portfolio reproductions of Owiti's art.
  - Art sale correspondence., 1984-1985; (4 items). (Box 22, Folder 7)